乖狗狗
Good boy.
小心点  小心点
Watch it. Watch it.
弗兰克  不要这样
Frank, no.
早说了让你别这样做
Told you not to do that.
-给点零钱吧  -不好意思  伙计
- Spare any change? - Whoa! Uh, sorry, man.
我一块钱都没有  我
Uh, I don't have any money. I just...
那好吧
Yeah, right.
对不起  兄弟
Whoa. Sorry, bro.
长点眼  伙计
Watch it, man.
嘿  想一起抵制气候变暖吗
Hey, stop global warming?
不好意思  我不会说英语
So sorry. No speak English.
-好吧  -对不起
- Okay. - So sorry.
打扰一下  想联名呼吁抵制气候变暖吗
Excuse me. Would you like to sign this to stop global warming?
别吹了
Shut up!
我在做噩梦
I'm having bad dreams
我睁眼躺着
I lie awake...
哦  你会永远这样的
Oh, you're taking forever!
她回来了吗
She's back?
-出去  -我不要再去车里面睡了
- Out. - I'm not sleeping in my car again.
-里面闻起来就像屎一样  -出去
- It smells like Hot Pockets and feet. - Get out.
我只是想来换个内裤
I just want clean underwear.
这也是我的房间啊
It's my room, too.
老天鹅啊  接电话  瑞恩
Oh, my God. Answer me, Ryan.
怎么了
What?
瑞恩  老兄  我的天啊
Ryan, dude, oh, my God.
快来找我  伙计  这太疯狂了
Get over here right now, man. This is crazy.
我的天呐  你不会相信这事的
Oh, my God. You're not gonna believe this.
你傻吗  我至少懂一点点吧
Fool, I understood two percent of that.
老兄  快过来吧
Dude, just come now!
哪里
Where?
-老兄  老兄  -怎么了
- Dude! Dude. - What?
你得马上进来看看
You need to get in here right now. Huh?
-最好别是什么坏事  -当然是好事
- This better be good, man. - It is.
快点  快来
Come on, come on.
-哇哦  -没骗你吧
- Whoa. - Right?
0.7米勒顿的能量
.7 millinewtons of energy.
天呐  这  这看起来可是大发现
God, that's... that's, like, huge.
-什么时候发现的  -昨天12:01
- When? - Uh, yesterday. 12:01 A.M.
天呐  这也太疯狂了  伙计
Damn, this is crazy, man.
没错瑞恩  但不知道是什么触发了设备
Yeah, but, Ryan, we have no idea what set the device off.
我是说  实验室是锁着的
Like, lab was locked.
就好像是设备自己运作了
It's almost like it decided to fire on its own.
就是这样吧  我受够了
That's it! I've had it!
哦  糟糕
Oh, shit.
嘿  你们要去哪里
Hey. Wh... Where you guys going?
-餐厅有教堂日活动  -开吃喽
- It's churro day at the cafeteria. - Nom, nom.
布洛森院长  你好啊
Dean Bronson, hi.
领带不错  上面那些是猫咪吗
Love the tie. Uh, are those cats?
是土耳其安哥拉猫  不要转移话题
Turkish angora. Uh, d- don't change the subject.
-什么话题  -那个
- What subject? - That.
我们有4个设备突然断电
We've had four rolling blackouts,
电路都被烧坏了
fried electrical circuits,
还烧坏了学校所有的灯泡
broken bulbs all over campus.
而这一切都归功于你的小实验
And it's all because of your little science project.
-这是我论文的项目  -是必然的失败
- It's my thesis project. - It's an abject failure.
我们大学的科学部门
This university's science department
因开拓超前思维并能产生成果而自豪
prides itself on pioneering forward-thinking ideas that yield results.
最后将成果转化为专利权
Results that lead to patents.
你看不出这其中的缘由吗
Do you see how it works?
就是为了钱吗
So, it's just about money?
没错  凡先生
Yes, Mr. Phan.
我并不想粉碎你的幻想
I hate to shatter your illusions,
但是总得有人打开天窗说亮话
but somebody has to keep the lights on around here,
你的实验项目必须马上停止
something you seem hell-bent on stopping!
彻底停止  就当这项目被悬停了吧
Literally! Consider this joke of a project suspended,
停止指令立即生效
effective immediately.
-什么  -就是这样
- What? - That's right.
我已经给伯纳教授打了电话
I've already called Professor Boner.
是邦纳
It's pronounced "Bonner."
他完全赞同我的要求
And he's in total agreement with my request.
我已经让保安人员今天6点钟来收走
I'm sending security to come and collect
你这吸收能量的破玩意儿
this energy-sucking doohickey by 6:00 today.
你不能就这样把它带走
You can't just take her.
好好听我说  我建议你尽快打包带走
Watch me. I suggest you wrap up
你留在这里的东西  收到了吗
whatever business you have left here, capisce?
有人吗
Hello?
搞什么鬼
What the hell?
(止步  限制区域  仅相关人员可入内  房间156  2号实验室)
嘿  恶心的家伙
Hey, shit bags.
你在玩偷拍小游戏的同时
While you were off playing games,
我的实验项目被勒令停止了
our project got shut down.
这下你开心了吗
I hope you're happy.
你发什么神经
What is wrong with you?
-干嘛偷偷摸摸过来  -我给你带了个
- Why are you sneaking up on me? - I was bringing you a...
这下好了  沾满细菌了
Well, now it's covered in bacteria,
两美元就这么浪费掉了
so that's two dollars wasted.
太无情了
So ungrateful.
乖狗狗
Good boy.
弗兰克  不要这样
Frank, no.
小伙子  你什么毛病
Dude, what's your problem?
对不起  伙计  我
I'm so sorry, man. I...
真的对不起
So sorry.
混球
Dick.
不好意思  兄弟
Sorry, bro.
别吹了
Shut up!
我在做噩梦
I'm having bad dreams
我睁眼躺着
I lie awake...
哦  你会永远这样的
Oh, you're taking forever!
出去
Out.
瑞恩
Ryan.
老兄  我现在应该是在梦游
Dude, I am tripping right now.
是的  没错
Yeah, no shit.
不  不  不  我说认真的
No. No, no, seriously.
我有那种能力  你知道吗
I'm having that thing. You know?
该怎么说呢  就像是感觉已经
What's it called? When you feel like you've already
经历过现在发生的一切
lived through something before.
-昨日重来的感觉吗  -就是这个感觉
- Déjà vu? - Yes, that.
感觉我从头到尾经历过今天这一切了
I feel like I've totally lived through this day already.
老天鹅啊  接电话  瑞恩
Oh, my God. Answer me, Ryan.
瑞恩  老兄  我的天啊
Ryan, dude, oh, my God.
快来找我  伙计
Get over here right now, man.
这太疯狂了  我的天呐
This is crazy. Oh, my God.
我  我等会儿打给你
I- I got to call you back.
好的  深呼吸
Okay. Just breathe.
呼吸
Just breathe.
听我说
Listen to me.
你死那天的经历又重来了一遍  对吗
The day reset when you died, right?
是的  有个疯子戴着婴儿面具攻击了我
Yeah. Some psycho dude in a baby mask attacked me.
但那只是一个梦  对吗
But it was just a dream, right?
-汤布斯死了  -罗丽也是
- Tombs is dead. - So is Lori.
那这次谁是凶手
Then who's the killer this time?
能听我说吗
Uh, hello.
你们谁能告诉我这他妈的到底是怎么了
Will someone please explain what the hell is going on?
好吧  再说一遍
Okay. Recap.
我在不停地重复经历同一天
So, I was stuck reliving the same day,
18号  星期一  一遍又一遍地经历
Monday the 18th, over and over and over again
直到一个戴着诡异娃娃脸面具的人
until someone wearing a Bayfield Baby mask
在我生日那天晚上杀了我
murdered me on the night of my birthday.
我起初完全不知道那是谁
I had no idea who it was
因为我是点婊
because I was such a crazy bitch
有太多的人对我恨之入骨
and so many people hated my guts.
在卡特的建议下  我列了个嫌疑人名单
So, at Carter's suggestion, I made a list of suspects.
最后发现凶手原来是我室友  罗丽
Turns out it was my roommate, Lori,
她一直在帮一个连环杀手逃出医院
who kept on helping a serial killer escape from the hospital,
希望看起来像是那个杀手杀了我
hoping it would look like he murdered me when,
但实际上一直都是她
in fact, it was her all along,
而这一切就因为她嫉妒我和
and all because she was jealous of an affair I was having
大学已婚的格瑞格里教授有一腿
with my college professor, Gregory, who was married.
是的  我知道这太不要脸了
Yeah, I know. Pretty shitty.
但是  无论如何
But, anyways,
我最终还是将罗丽踢出窗外  杀死了她
I finally kicked Lori's crazy ass out a window and killed her,
从而终止了时间循环  我是这么想的
which broke the loop, or so I thought.
但现在看起来  时间循环传到了你这里
But now it only looks like it passed the loop on to you
而你将会不停的重复这一切
and you're gonna be stuck reliving this day
直到我们想出办法
until we figure out how to stop it.
当然了
Of course.
我还在做梦吧
I'm still dreaming.
等等  你说什么
Wait. What?
这就像《盗梦空间》
It's like Inception.
梦中还有梦
It's a dream within a dream.
老兄  你可不是在做梦
Bro, you're not dreaming.
-瑞恩  我们  -嘘
- Ryan, we... - Shh.
我在试着让自己醒过来
I'm trying to wake myself up.
看见没  这不是梦境
There. See? You're not dreaming.
你为什么打我的鸡鸡
Why'd you hit my penis?
你怎么反应这么大
Why are you acting like this?
你打了我的鸡鸡  这太粗鲁了
You smacked my dick. That's rude.
我都没碰到你
I barely touched you.
好吧  告诉我你在哪里死的
Okay. Show me where you died.
在那后面  储物柜那里
Back there. Storage closet.
嘿  把棒球棍给我
Hey. Give me that.
我自己能行
I can handle myself.
你还没死够吗
You've died enough, haven't you?
-给他致命一击  -嘘
- Bash his head in. - Shh!
(我丢你老母的)
-萨玛  你个混球  -你为什么打我
- Samar, you asshole! - Why'd you hit me?
你为什么在我后面偷偷摸摸的
Why do you keep sneaking up on me?
我觉得我颧骨断了
Ah, I think my cheekbone's broken.
这里发生了什么
What is happening in here?
瑞恩打断了我的颧骨
Ryan broke my cheekbone.
-凶手是他吗  -不是
- Was it him? - No.
上次我死的时候他就在我眼前
He was here when I died before.
什么
What?
你从哪里拿到的面具
Where'd you get that mask?
它就在楼道里啊
It was just laying in the hallway.
不知道谁扔在那里的
Somebody must have dropped it.
就这样吧  我受够了
That's it. I've had it.
等等  你们去哪里
Wait, wait. Where you going?
-餐厅有教堂日活动  -开吃喽
- Uh, churro day at the cafeteria. - Nom, nom.
我们有4个设备突然断电
We've had four rolling blackouts,
电路都被烧坏了
fried electrical circuits,
还烧坏了学校所有的灯泡
broken bulbs all over campus.
而这一切都归功于你的小实验
And it's all because of your little science project.
等等
Wait.
什么小实验
What science project?
西西弗斯量子冷却反应堆
The Sisyphus Quantum Cooling Reactor.
我们简称西西装置
We call it Sissy for short.
看到这些了吗
You see all these?
这是质子发射器
They're proton lasers.
设备被激活的时候  会冷却那个离心机
And when they fire, they cool the centrifuge right here
热量接近到10的负9次方开尔文
to almost below one nanokelvin.
可以说  我们正试着证明时间
So, basically, we're trying to prove that time
可以在分子级别被减速
can be slowed down on a molecular level.
现在虽然还没有见效
It hasn't worked yet,
但就在一个晚上这个设备被激活的时候
but we did find some promising data
我们发现了一些有力的数据
after the device fired the other night.
什么时候
When?
昨天早上12:01
12:01 A.M. yesterday.
18号  星期一那天
Monday the 18th.
怎么了
What?
你创造了这个时间循环  白痴
You created the time loop, dummy.
这不可能
That's impossible.
这可不是设计西西装置的设计初衷啊
That's not what Sissy was designed to do.
我不知道该说什么
I don't know what to tell you.
也许我们刚好发现了
Well, maybe we're just discovering
它真正的功能
what it actually does.
一个猝不及防的结果
An unintended reaction.
也许我们认为可以将时间减速
Maybe we thought we were slowing time,
但实际上我们让它循环了
but what if we looped it instead?
所以说你卡在今天了
Now you're stuck in this day.
祝贺你
Congrats.
顺便提醒你  你会死
Oh, and by the way, you're gonna die
一遍又一遍地死
again and again and again.
卡特  告诉你女朋友不要再来吓我了
Carter, tell your girlfriend to stop trying to scare me.
她不算我女朋友
Oh, she's not my girlfriend.
-等等  你是我女朋友吗  -算是吧
- Well, wait, are you my girlfriend? - Kinda.
嘿  伙计们
Hey, guys,
能暂时放下你们之间的关系问题吗
are you done talking about your relationship status?
因为她刚刚说了我会死
Because she just said I'm gonna die.
而你得尽快找办法去停止时间循环
And you need to figure out how to close the loop
不然那个杀手会再次杀了你
before the killer finds you again.
但我不知道发生了什么啊
But I don't know how it happened.
那个设备就自己运行了
It just fired on its own.
我的天
Oh, God.
丹妮尔  你好啊
Danielle. Hi.
-你去哪里了  -什么意思
- Where were you? - What do you mean?
你没参加我们的寝室会
You ditched our house meeting.
-不是取消了吗  -什么时候的事
- It was canceled. - When?
在我把杀人的室友踢出窗外之后
Um, after I kicked my murdering roommate out of a window.
没错  是谁天天向卡帕祈祷
Exactly. Who's gonna pledge Kappa
说我们中了死亡诅咒
now that we have a death curse?
还说我们现在很危险  翠
We're in crisis mode, Tree.
这些都是什么人
Who are these people?
你好
Hi.
呃  我是  我是萨玛
Uh, I'm- I'm- I'm Samar.
嘿  萨莫萨  眼睛看哪里呢
Hey, Samosa, my head's the middle one.
不管怎样  在你们的诡异会谈弄完之后
Anyhoo, call me as soon as you're done
尽快给我打电话
with your creepy little Comic-Con meeting. Ugh.
她刚刚叫我"萨莫萨"吗
Did she just call me "samosa"?
是的
Yep.
-你觉得她喜欢萨莫萨吗  -不喜欢
- You think she likes samosas? - Nope.
伙计们  别分心  我还不想死
Guys, focus. I don't want to die.
乐观点来说  你会复活的
On the bright side, you'll come back.
我死了11次
I died 11 times.
11次吗  他奶奶的
11? Hell no.
-被杀很疼的  -等等
- That shit hurts. - Wait a minute.
伙计们  我有个主意
Guys, I have an idea.
我们只要找个最安全的地方
We just need to find the safest possible place
然后在那里等杀手不就行了吗
and wait it out there.
哪里呢
Where?
怎么了
What?
人山人海的地方不就挺安全的吗
There's... safety in numbers.
还不如说是躲在众目睽睽之下
More like hiding in plain sight.
哪个鬼才选的诡异娃娃脸面具来当吉祥物
Who picks a creepy baby for a mascot anyway?
早知道就去麻省理工了
I knew I should have gone to M.I.T.
他走步违规了吧
He traveled!
三不沾喽
Airball!
那是你和你妈妈吗
Is that you and your mom?
太有爱了
That's cute.
我在想
I was thinking.
这太讽刺了
It's ironic.
我想  因为某些莫名其妙的原因
Here I thought I was stuck in the same day
我困在同一天了
for some big cosmic reason.
你知道吗  面对妈妈的死亡
You know, facing my mom's death.
却无能为力
It had nothing to do with her.
结果却发现这只是一个科学的意外
Turns out it was just some big scientific fluke.
但这并没有失去它的意义  不是吗
That doesn't make it mean any less, does it?
是吧
I guess not.
你那里沾了点东西
Oh, you got a little something right here.
好了
Yep, uh, uh.
是吗
Yeah.
对不起  这
Sorry. It's...
你这太老套了
You're such a grandpa.
是啊  但你还是上当了
Yeah, well, you fell for it, so...
请大家从最近的出口离开
Please make your way to the nearest exit
保持好秩序
in an orderly fashion.
这不是演习
This is not a drill.
请大家从最近的出口离开
Please make your way to the nearest exit
保持好秩序
in an orderly fashion.
重复  这不是演习
Again, this is not a drill.
嘿  小心点
Hey, watch it!
伙计们  等等我
Guys! Wait up!
别推我
Don't push me.
嘿  我找不到手机了
Hey, I can't find my phone.
救我  帮帮我  求求你们
Help! Help! Please!
救救我
Help!
-什么人  -来下面
- What was that? - Down here!
见鬼
Holy shit.
你还好吗
Are you okay?
应该没问题
Yeah, I think so.
厉害啊  做的不错
Well, damn. Good job.
-我之前可是练过的  -搞什么呢
- I have a little practice. - What the hell?
我还以为你是凶手
I thought you were the killer.
你该出声说句话的
You should have said something.
我刚刚在找你
I was looking for you.
那  这是谁
Well, who is it?
只有一个办法能知道了
Only one way to find out.
什么鬼
What the fu...
你确定你  你没有双胞胎兄弟吗
You sure you... you don't have a twin brother?
也许你们出生的时候就被分开了
Maybe you were separated at birth.
当然  我很确定
Of course I'm sure.
-见鬼  -确实是"见鬼"了
- Oh, shit. - "Oh, shit" is right.
你是谁
Who are you?
你觉得我是谁  呆子
Who you think I am, dummy?
就是你
It's you.
-废话  -废话
- Duh. - Duh.
这到底是什么情况
What the hell is going on here?
听着  我在试图关闭时间循环
Look, I was trying to close the loop,
但是我莫名其妙地进入了平行时间循环
but somehow I got knocked into a parallel time loop.
我们现在都非常危险
We're all in serious danger.
我们在同一空间出现的时间越长
The longer we exist in the same dimension,
就会发生越糟糕的事情
the worse things will get.
就像是蝴蝶效应
It's a butterfly effect.
你必须杀了他
You have to kill him.
-杀了我吗  -如果你们不阻止他
- Me? - He's going to create bigger problems
他会给大家带来更大的麻烦
if you do not stop him.
杀了他
Kill him now!
不  去他妈的  杀了他
No, screw that. Kill him.
你们是在浪费时间  快动手
You're wasting your time. Do it.
老兄  我才是你的朋友  他不是
Dude, I'm your friend, not him.
算了吧  去他妈的
Uh... you know what? Screw this.
我自己来处理我自己吧
I'll just take care of it myself.
-阻止他啊  -瑞恩  也许你该住手
- Stop him. - Wait. Ryan, maybe you should stop.
看看他  是他疯了
Look at him. He's crazy.
我设计了这东西  我知道自己在干什么
I'm the one who designed this. I know what I'm doing.
你不明白你在做什么
You don't understand what you're doing!
闭嘴  假瑞恩
Shut up, fake Ryan!
瑞恩  这感觉可不太对
Ryan, this doesn't feel right.
瑞恩  住手
Ryan, stop.
但是秒差距是距离单位  不是时间单位
But a parsec is a measure of distance, not time.
好吧  你觉得汉索罗是个骗子吗
Okay, so now you're gonna call Han Solo a liar?
不  我是说如果凯瑟尔竞赛说的是
No, I'm saying if a normal Kessel Run is...
隹  救我
Dre, help me.
快点
Come on!
老兄  你又给我饮料下药了吗
Dude, did you dose my Yoo-hoo again?
我是怎么跟你说的  不要打开那个东西
What did I tell you about turning that thing on?
快把它关掉  现在立刻马上
Turn it off now. Turn it off now!
抓住他  抓住那个人
Just get him. Get him. Get the man.
抓住他  抓住他啊
Get him, get him, get him!
退后  让开
Back off! Back...
瑞恩  你就把它关掉吧
Ryan, just turn it off, man.
瑞恩  你在干嘛啊
Ryan, what are you doing?
伙计们  把他手里的扳手给我拿走
Guys, take the wrench from him.
连个学生都搞不定吗
He's a college student.
只是个扳手
It's just a wrench.
别被他吓到了
Don't be scared of him.
好的  好吧  拔掉电源的插头
Okay, all right, just unplug it.
断开电源  拔插头
Unplug the machine. Unplug it!
不
No!
别吹了
Shut up!
嘿  你醒了
Oh, hey. You're up.
我不太确定你是否想多睡会儿
Yeah, I wasn't sure if you wanted to sleep in or not,
-所以我  -♪耶  今天是我的生日
- so I... -♪ Yeah, it's my birthday
-♪我才不打算接电  -翠
-♪ And I ain't gotta pick up the pho... - Tree?
他妈的别这样
No fucking way.
我帮你叠好了衣服
Hey, I... I folded your clothes for you.
瑞恩  给我滚进来
Ryan! Get in here right now!
等等  你们互相认识吗
Wait a minute, you two know each other?
-认识 -不认识
- Yes. - No.
瑞恩  你这个混球
Ryan, you dumbass!
你把我送回来了
You sent me back.
-什么  -今天是18号  星期一
- What? - It's Monday the 18th.
我简直不敢相信
I don't believe this.
我本来跳出了循环  你怎么能这么对我
I just got out. How could you do this to me?
这个神经女是谁
Uh... who's this crazy white girl?
也许这只是个噩梦什么的
Maybe it was a-a bad dream or something.
你说的对  是个噩梦
You're right. It is a bad dream.
是个梦魇
It's a nightmare!
这太糟糕了
This sucks!
这简直太扯淡了
It sucks the biggest mega balls
简直是霉到家了
in the history of shitty ball-suckery!
这
It...
我没事
I'm okay.
你确定吗
You sure?
确定
Yes.
只是他必须弥补这一切
He just needs to fix this.
就现在
Now.
你们在开玩笑  对吗
This is a joke, right?
我希望是开玩笑
I wish.
听着
Look.
瑞恩  我们得去你的实验室
Ryan, we need to go to your lab,
打开西西装置
turn on Sissy,
然后想办法把我送回去
and figure out how to send me back.
你是怎么知道西西装置的
Uh, how do you know about Sissy?
我的天  别管那么多
Oh, my God. Just...
快走
Let's go.
跟上来啊  傻子们
Ándale, people!
嘿  想一起抵制气候变暖吗
Hey. Stop global warming?
说一句"不了  谢谢"不行吗
A simple "no, thanks" would do!
对不起
Sorry!
这他妈的就是同一天  同一天
This is the same day, same day,
同一天  同一天  又是同一天
same day, same day, same day!
∮ 墙上有62个啤酒罐 ∮
∮ 62 bottles of beer on the wall
我听不见你说什么
I can't hear you!
∮ 62个啤酒罐 ∮
∮ 62 bottles of beer
∮ 你摘下一个  传一圈 ∮
∮ You take one down, pass it around
-继续  -♪墙上有61个啤酒罐
- Keep going! -♪ 61 bottles of beer on the wall...
嘿  你还没回我
Hey, you haven't returned any of...
你是个基佬
You are gay.
等等  你要去哪里
Wait, where are you going?
实验室要走这边
The lab's back that way.
我有点事要先处理一下
I have some business to take care of first.
鬼鬼祟祟的小婊砸
You sneaky little beyatch.
怪了
That's weird.
什么
What?
她本该在这里的
She was supposed to be here.
谁
Who?
呃  没什么
Uh, never mind.
可算回来了
She finally rolls in.
它在哪里
Where is it?
什么在哪里
Where's what?
-你好  卡特  -你好
- Oh, hey, Carter. - Hey.
纸杯蛋糕在哪里
Where's the cupcake?
什么纸杯蛋糕
What cupcake?
你为我生日做的那个
The one you made for my birthday.
你下毒了的那个
The one you poisoned.
那个纸杯蛋糕啊
Oh, that cupcake.
我认真的
I'm serious.
听着  我不知道丹妮尔跟你开了
Look, I don't know what stupid joke
什么愚蠢的玩笑  但没有什么纸杯蛋糕
Danielle put you up to, but there's no cupcake.
抱歉
Sorry.
好了  我得走了  我要替珍上班去了
All right, I got to go. I'm pulling a double for Jen.
她得流感了
She's got the flu.
不过还是  祝你生日快乐
Happy birthday, though.
拜拜
Toodles.
不太对劲
Something's wrong.
怎么了
What?
我不知道
I don't know.
跟之前不一样了
It's different.
-有两个我吗  -对
- There were two of me? - Yes.
整件事就因此而起
That is how this whole thing happened.
知道吗  这让我想起了《回到未来2》
You know, this kind of reminds me of Back to the Future II.
-没错  -对吧
- Totally. - Right?
-马迪·麦克弗莱出演的  -还有博士
- You know, with Marty McFly? - Doc?
-迪罗伦呢  -听不懂
- The DeLorean? - Sorry.
你认真的吗  你没看过《回到未来》吗
Are you serious? You've never seen Back to the Future?
没有  我
No, I...
-你是怎么  -等等
- How do you... - Wait.
天啊
Oh, my God.
这是不是意味着
Does this mean that...
这是不是意味着会有两个我
Does this mean that there are two of me?
我对此高度怀疑
I highly doubt it.
要创造一个全息宇宙几乎是不可能的
It's almost impossible to create a holographic universe.
你可能是被困在一个量子循环维度里了
You're probably stuck in a quantum cyclic dimension.
这个维度里只有一个你
There's only one of you here,
因为另一个你被撞进
because the other you got knocked into
一个多元宇宙里的某个平行维度去了
a parallel dimension somewhere in the multiverse.
好的  瑞恩  谢谢你的解释
Okay, Ryan. Thanks for clearing that up.
真是太有用了呢
That was super helpful.
你从没听过多元宇宙论吗
You never heard the multiverse theory?
我看起来像是知道多元宇宙是什么的人吗
Do I look like someone who knows what a multiverse is?
好吧  听着  这是我们的宇宙
Okay, look. This is our universe.
明白吗  好好看着
Okay? Now, look.
理论上  宇宙有六个维度
In theory, the universe has six dimensions.
那么  如果你说的是真的
Now, if what you're saying is true,
也许你在同一天醒来
then maybe you woke up on the same day...
却不在同一个维度里
but not in the same dimension.
这就可以解释那些异常现象了
That would explain the anomalies.
所以  有多异常呢
So, how different are we talking here?
那就看情况了
Well, it depends.
糟糕  我把寝室会给忘了
Oh, shit. I forgot our house meeting.
丹妮尔  抱歉  我只是
Danielle, I'm sorry. I just...
嘿  宝贝
Hey, babe.
你好吗
You doing all right?
你好  瑞
Hi, Ry.
你好  丹妮尔
Hey, Danielle.
我演的像吗
Did that look real?
我正在为今年的
I'm auditioning for this year's production
《奇迹缔造者》的试镜做准备
of The Miracle Worker.
你知道安妮·弗兰克又聋又瞎吗
Did you know Anne Frank was blind and deaf?
是海伦·凯勒
Uh... Helen Keller.
你说什么
Excuse me?
安妮·弗兰克是那个在阁楼的女孩
Anne Frank was in the attic.
这样啊
Oh.
管他呢
Whatever.
我只知道装瞎就行了
All I know is acting blind
可能比真瞎还要难
is probably harder than actually being blind.
我是说  它需要演技
I mean, the skill set it takes.
梅丽尔·斯特里普为了准备这个角色
Meryl Streep taped her eyelids shut
把她的眼皮都粘住了
just to prepare for a role.
对了  今天有人错过了我们的寝室会
Well. Somebody missed our house meeting today.
我很抱歉  我
I'm sorry. I...
我开玩笑的
Totes kidding.
小寿星有豁免权
Birthday girls get a free pass.
话说回来  我们选定了今年的慈善主题
Anyhoo, we picked this year's charity.
我要宣布了哦
Are you ready for it?
我们要再办一次募捐艺术展
We're doing the special needs art fair again.
真棒
Oh. Nice.
你这可是大善举  丹妮尔
You do so much good, Danielle.
我很佩服你
I-I really admire that.
拜托别这样  看到那些小脸儿
Oh, please. It just warms my heart
我的心都要化了
seeing all those little faces.
我是说  你们别理解错了
I mean, don't get me wrong.
有时候他们抱着你久久不放
Sometimes they try to hug you too long,
确实有点让人不舒服
and it gets a little uncomfortable,
但习惯就好了
but you just get used to it.
说到底
And at the end of the day,
人生中没有什么馈赠
there is no greater gift in life
能比孩子们的爱再珍贵的了
than the love of a child.
谢谢你
Thank you.
翠
Tree?
你还好吗
You okay?
呃  我没事  我
Uh... yeah, I...
∮ 耶  今天是我的生日 ∮
∮ Yeah, it's my birthday
-♪我才不打算接电话  -抱歉
- ♪And I ain't gotta pick up the phone. - Sorry.
嘿  爸爸
Hey, Dad. Um...
呃  对  对
Uh... Yeah, yeah.
抱歉  我这就来
Sorry. I'm on my way.
我马上就到
I'll be there in a little bit.
我得走了
I have to go. Um...
等一下  什么  你要走了吗
Wait, what? You're leaving?
对  我得去和我爸爸吃午饭
Uh, yeah. I have to meet up with my dad for lunch.
生日惯例
It's a birthday thing.
三点钟在实验室见
Meet me in the lab at 3:00.
在事情变得更糟糕前  赶紧想点办法
We are figuring this out before it gets any worse!
-嘿  爸爸  -嘿
- Hey, Dad. - Hey.
-抱歉我来晚了  -没事的 宝贝
- Sorry I'm late. - It's okay, sweetie.
一整天都怪怪的
It's just been a weird day.
-一切都好吗  -还好
- Everything okay? - Uh, yeah.
每天也都那样  你知道的
It's just... stuff, you know.
在学校过的怎么样
How's school?
还好吧  爸爸
Um, it's fine, Dad.
-可以点餐了吗  -稍等
- Are you ready to order? - Not yet.
我们还要等一个人
We're still waiting on one more.
还有一个人吗  我
One more? I...
好的  那我稍后再来
Okay. I'll be right back.
妈妈
Mom.
Mom!
你好
Hi.
你来了
You're here.
你真的来了
Oh, you're really here.
我当然要来  今天可是我们的大日子
Well, of course I'm here. It's our day.
你还好吗
Are you okay?
好  当然好
Yeah. Yeah.
天啊  我没事  我只是
Oh, God, I'm fine. I'm just...
见到你真好
It's good to see you.
好了
Okay.
现在试试吧
Try it now.
20秒
20 seconds.
发生这些算正常吗
Yo, is this normal?
别担心  不会再爆炸了
Don't worry, it's not gonna blow up again.
-你说"再"吗  -十  九
- Again? - Ten. Nine.
八  七
Eight. Seven.
六  五
Six. Five.
四  三
Four. Three.
二
Two.
停下
Stop!
快停下
Leave it.
-是你让我  -我知道
- You told me to... - No, I-I know.
我改变主意了
I changed my mind.
这一定就是那个神经女了
This must be the crazy white girl.
嘿  翠  等一下
Hey, Tree. Wait up.
嘿  等下
Hey. Hey.
你怎么改变主意了
Why the change of heart?
-一切都不一样了  -什么不一样了
- Everything's different. - Different how?
等等  你打算什么时候告诉我
Wait, when were you gonna tell me?
告诉你什么
Tell you what?
丹妮尔的事
About Danielle.
丹妮尔怎么了
Yeah, what about Danielle?
显然你们两个在一起了
Apparently you guys are dating.
等等  我以为  我以为你知道的
Wait, I thought... I thought you knew that.
我是说  你们住在一起
I mean, you guys live in the same house.
不知道  我绝对不知道
Uh, no, I definitely didn't know.
但最大的问题是  她知道吗
But the bigger question is: does she know?
她知道什么
Does she know what?
她最好的朋友之一早上是在你床上醒来的
One of her closest friends woke up in your bed this morning.
你不觉得应该告诉她吗
You don't think that that's newsworthy?
什么都没发生啊
Nothing happened.
我昨晚睡的是瑞恩的床
I slept in Ryan's bed last night.
所以  为什么带我回家呢
So, why take me home?
因为你  因为你醉倒了
Because you were... you were wasted.
我怕你摔倒
I was afraid you were gonna fall
或者跟詹尼斯·乔普林一样被呕吐物呛到
or choke on your own vomit like Janis Joplin.
好吧
Okay.
没关系  没事的
It's fine. It's fine. It's fine.
没关系  本来就应该这样
It's fine. This is how it's supposed to be.
我妈妈没事  罗丽没有想杀我
My mom's okay. Lori isn't trying to kill me.
这个版本的人生更好
I mean, this is, like, the better version
-不是吗  -你在
- of my life, right? - What are you...
她在联谊会里  格瑞格里  她
She's in a sorority, Gregory. She's...
等一下  难道
Wait a minute. In this...
在这个维度里  我们
in this other dimension, were we...
我先不跟你说了
I... I can't do this right now.
别这样  翠
No, Tr... Tree!
你准备好了吗
Are you ready for this?
好了  拿着这个
I... No. Okay. Hold this.
然后
And...
我的天
Oh, my God!
太奇怪了
It's so weird.
太好吃了
Oh, my... this is amazing.
但我觉得你不能再吃了
But I don't think you have to get another one.
这是我吃过最棒的
This is, like, the best...
这些记忆没有一个是属于我的
None of these memories are mine.
我知道这是你的  我就今晚借一下
I know. I'm just borrowing it for tonight.
你什么时候去派对呢
What time you going to the party?
我  我不能去了
Um... I, uh... I can't make it.
-出了一些事情  -什么情况
- Something came up. - What?
我是说
I mean,
我们已经为这个准备好几周了  翠
we've been planning this for weeks, Tree.
我知道  我知道这是一个惊喜派对
No, I know. And I know it's a surprise party.
我很抱歉  只是
I'm sorry. It's just...
我的父母来城里了  我需要
You know, my parents are in town, and I need to...
我们交的学费也该起作用了
Ugh. Our tuition dollars at work.
总之  谁告诉你有一个惊喜派对的
Anyhoo, who told you about the surprise?
是罗丽吗
Was it Lori?
我发誓  那个女孩
I swear, that girl
真的需要学会如何保守秘密
really needs to learn how to keep a secret.
我不知道你是怎么了
I don't know what's going on with you...
你知道吗  翠  我就跟你直说吧
You know what, Tree, I'm just gonna come out and say it.
我感觉特别的
I have been feeling so extremely
-不被你欣赏  -报道一则枪击案
- unappreciated by you... - ...following a deadly shootout
发生于今早导致一名警员死亡
this morning that left one officer dead.
你在听吗
Hello?
我在跟你说话呢
I'm still talking to you.
汤布斯正在被全国追捕
Tombs was the subject of a nationwide manhunt
他在五个月里横跨四个州
that ended after a five-month pursuit across four state lines
杀害了六名女性
that left six female victims.
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
他还在这里
He's still here.
他要逃跑了  赶紧报警
He's going to escape! Call the police!
谁要跑了
Who?
约翰·汤布斯  赶紧报警
John Tombs. Just call the police.
-什么情况  -等一下  别进去
- What? - Wait! Don't go in there!
该死
Shit.
你等下  你在做什么
Excuse me. What are you doing?
放下斧子
Whoa. Drop the ax.
-等等  我可以解  -马上放下斧子
- Wait. I can expl... - Drop it now.
他已经逃跑了  他要杀人了
He's escaped. He's gonna kill someone.
-面对墙站好  -你不明白  罗丽要
- Face up against the wall. - No, you don't understand. Lori...
我不会问第二遍
I'm not asking again.
请你听我解释
Please listen to me.
我的舍友在这里工作
My roommate works here.
她放走了汤布斯因为她想要陷害他
She set Tombs free because she's trying to blame him,
但是她要杀了我
but she's gonna kill me.
我不知道你嗑了什么药  女士
I don't know what kind of shit you're on, lady,
但是汤布斯现在正在手术室里
but Tombs is down in the O.R. right now.
护士刚刚带走他
Nurse just took him.
那护士是不是很高  深黑头发梳着马尾
Was she tall, dark hair and a ponytail?
我们走吧
Let's go.
我知道你觉得我疯了  但是你得相信我
I know you think I'm crazy, but you got to believe me.
派遣中心  我是康罗警官
Dispatch, this is Officer Conrow.
医院里有人袭警
Have an 11-55 at the hospital.
需要紧急支援
Need immediate assistance.
快点啊
Come on.
我知道是你  罗丽
I know it's you, Lori!
-什么情况  -我的天啊
- What? - Oh, my God!
我的天啊  我以为你是
Oh, my God. I thought you were the...
你没事吧  这他妈的发生什么了
Are you okay? What the hell is going on?
-那是谁  -汤布斯逃走了
- Who was that? - Tombs escaped.
他想杀了我
He's trying to kill me.
不可能  那是不可能的  翠
No, Tree, that's not possible.
我刚刚把他推到手术室去
I just took him down to the O.R.
发生什么了
What's happening?
我不知道
I-I don't know.
我的天啊  他把电断了
Oh, my God, he cut the power.
保持冷静
Just stay calm.
保持冷静  该死
Just stay calm. Shit!
好吧  把门拉开吧
Okay. Come on.
过来吧
Come on.
我们这是在哪
Where the hell are we?
这里肯定是待建楼层
This must be one of the floors under construction.
快点  在另一头肯定有紧急出口
Come on. There's an emergency exit on the other end.
等一下
Wait.
把那个拿上
Grab that.
好的
Okay.
怎么了
What?
你听到什么了吗
Did you hear something?
好吧  混蛋  让我看看你有什么能耐
All right, asshole, let's see what you got.
该死
Shit!
别吹了
Shut up!
太菜了  翠
Rookie move, Tree.
嘿  你醒了
Oh, hey. You're up.
我在哪一个维度
What dimension am I in?
丹妮尔
Danielle.
我女朋友吗
Uh, my girlfriend?
还是那个维度
Same one.
-♪耶  今天是我的生日
-♪ Yeah, it's my birthday
∮ 我才不打算接电话 ∮
∮ And I ain't gotta pick up the pho...
你没事吧
Are you okay?
没事
Yeah.
好的不能再好了
Never better.
我帮你叠好了衣服  所以
Hey, I folded your clothes for you, so...
听着  无意冒犯
Look, no offense,
但是你怎么可能和她在一起呢
but how could you possibly end up with her?
和谁啊
With who?
丹妮尔
Danielle.
因为  她很好相处
Uh, uh, she's nice.
好吧  "好相处"
Oh, "nice."
等一下
Wait a minute.
她难道不是  你最好的朋友吗
Isn't she, like, your best friend?
老兄  你是把那妞上了吗还是怎
Dude, did you hit that fine vagine or wha...
-这真有趣  -没有  我没做过任何
-Huh. Interesting. - No, I wasn't trying to do any...
-你不如你看起来那么单纯哦  -但是
- Not as innocent as you look. - But...
-什么  我  -你
- What? No, I-I... - You.
一小时后在你的实验室见
Meet me in your lab in an hour.
我不想再穿这些恶心的衣服了
I've got to get out of these disgusting clothes.
仔细听我说
Listen to me carefully.
我需要留在这个维度里
I need to stay here in this dimension.
明白吗  所以把时间循环关掉吧
Okay? So just close the loop.
听着  我们完全不知道
Look, we have no idea
这件事情一开始是怎么发生的
how this even happened in the first place.
你们不都是聪明的科学人士吗
Well, you're all brainy science people, right?
所以你们会弄明白的
So you'll figure it out.
你明白我们在折腾
You realize we're messing
一些我们从未接触过的事情  对吗
with things we have no business touching, right?
在你们开始搭建那巨大的蠢东西之前
Well, maybe you should have thought of that
你们就应该想到这一点
before you built the big dumb thing.
拜托  拜托帮我一个忙
Just... just please do me a favor
想想办法弄明白这个  好吗
and try to figure this out, okay?
求求你们了
Please.
听着  这会是一个反复试验的情况
Look, this is gonna be a trial-and-error situation.
我们需要排除每一个变量
We have to rule out every variable
来确定出最终可以结束循环的算法
in order to narrow down the correct algorithm that will close the loop.
-好吧  -但这是好多天
- Okay. - Uh, it's days,
甚至好几周的工作量
maybe weeks of work.
而且如果你说的是真的
And if what you're saying is true,
那么是没有办法记录我们实验进度的
there's no way to keep a record of our progress.
我没有听明白
I'm not following.
好吧
Okay. Um...
比如说我们要测试很多种变量
Say we test, like, dozens of variables.
在一天结束时  循环就重置了  对吗
By the end of the day, the loop will reset, right?
所以我们实验得出结论
So everything we learned gets...
都会被抹掉
...erased.
是没有办法可以让我们跟进进度的
There's no way for us to track our progress
简单因为我们不会记得
simply because we just don't remember
任何的实验结论
anything we learned.
所以我们就回到起点了
And we'll be back to square one.
真是太好了
Great.
我完蛋了
I'm screwed.
等下  我明白了
Wait, no, I got it.
你说所有事情都会重置
Okay, you said everything resets
除了你的记忆  对吗
but your memory, right?
-没错  -好吧  那
- Yeah. - All right, well, then...
你只需要变成一个人肉记录仪
you're just gonna have to be a living record.
等下  你是指记住所有事情吗
Wait, you mean memorize everything?
-没错  -这主意太有才了
- Yeah. - That's genius.
不行  不行  不行
No. No, no, no, no.
这主意一点都不有才  我不是科学家
That's not genius. I'm not a scientist.
而且  我想说  你知道
And hello. I mean, you do realize
有一个杀手在追杀我  对吗
there's a killer after me, right?
这意味着我需要一遍又一遍地死
That means I'm gonna have to die over and over again
直到你们弄明白如何关掉这个时间循环
until you guys figure out how to close the loop.
我是说  我觉得你可以
I mean, I guess you could
在他们找到你之前自杀
just kill yourself before they find you.
天啊  又一个有才的主意呢
Wow. Another genius idea.
总比被一个带着婴儿面具的疯子追杀好吧
Um, better than being chased by some crazy guy in a baby mask.
那你有更好的主意吗
I mean, do you have a better idea?
我就知道你会这么说
I knew you were gonna say that.
(错误算法)
∮ 我只想要  能正常醒来 ∮
∮ All that I want is to wake up fine
∮ 告诉我一切正常  我不会再次死去 ∮
∮ Tell me that I'm all right, that I ain't gonna die
别吹了
Ow. Shut up!
嘿  你醒了
Oh, hey. You're up.
-我不太确定  -我不太确定
- I wasn't sure if you wanted... - I wasn't sure
你是否想多睡会儿
if you wanted to sleep in or not.
我昨晚帮你叠好了衣服
I folded your clothes last night.
也不确定会不会把衣服折皱
Wasn't sure if that material gets wrinkled.
很好奇  你老是趴在那桌子下面
Anyway, what the hell are you always
翻什么呢
looking for under that desk?
找我的牙箍
Uh... oh, just... my mouth guard.
因为  我
Yeah, I...
我晚上磨牙
I grind my teeth at night.
解决了一个世界难题
Oh, mystery solved.
∮ 耶  今天是我的生日 ∮
∮ Yeah, it's my birthday
∮ 我才不打算接电 ∮
∮ And I ain't gotta pick up the pho...
你没事吧
You okay?
好的不能再好了
Yep. Never better.
你昨晚醉成那个样
I don't know if you remember my name or not.
也不知道还记不记得我的名字
You were, uh... you were pretty wasted last night.
我叫卡特
But I'm-I'm Carter.
你确定没事吗
Hey, are you sure you're okay?
你脸色死白死白的
You're looking kind of pale.
没事  我
No, I'm fine. I...
不对  我好像要晕过去了
Actually, I'm probably gonna pass out.
啥
What?
-完了  晕定了  -什么  别
- Yep. Definitely passing out. - What? No, uh...
你是把那妞上了吗还是怎
You hit that fine vagine or what?
她这是死了吗
Is she dead?
-瑞恩  过来帮帮忙  -好的
- Ryan, little help here, man. - Oh, okay.
别怕
Hey, hey. It's okay.
是我而已
It's just me.
你没事吧  之前可是真的吓到我了
You okay? You really gave me a scare back there.
嗯  我没事
Yeah. Yeah, I'm fine.
你还是来了
You still came.
当然会来了
Yeah, of course.
为什么会不来
Why wouldn't I?
我们联系了你父母
Oh, we got a hold of your parents.
他们马上就到
They're on their way.
不行  不能让他们来  这里不安全
No. They can't come here. It's not safe.
你说的是什么意思
What are you talking about?
吓死我了
Jesus.
你有事吗
Can I help you?
没关系  他是我朋友
Oh, it's okay. He's a friend.
对不起  探视时间结束了
Sorry. Visiting hours are over.
好吧  那我走了
All right. Well...
多谢了  卡特
Thanks, Carter.
早点好起来
Yeah. Feel better.
你现在知道我今天为什么没去上课了吧
So, I guess now you know why I wasn't in your class today.
对不起  你说什么
Pardon?
高阶生物
Advanced bio.
不好意思
Uh, I'm sorry.
你有选我的课吗
Are you in my class?
我对你不太脸熟
You don't look familiar.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我记错了
My mistake.
好吧
Right.
你好  我是巴特勒医生
Well, I'm Dr. Butler.
见到你很高兴
Nice to meet you.
格尔布曼女士  我有点看不明白
Ms. Gelbman, I've been having a hard time
你的病历
pulling up your medical records.
我知道  看病历我早该死了
I know. I should be dead.
我的检查结果不大对劲  是吧
My results, they don't make sense, right?
是的
Yes.
说真的  结果很不好
They're highly alarming, to be honest.
等等
Wait.
几点了
What time is it?
差不多九点半
Uh, it's almost 9:30.
她快死了
She's about to die.
-谁  -罗丽
- Who? - Lori.
-他要杀了她  -什么
- He's gonna kill her. - What?
听我说  你得阻止她去手术室
Listen to me. You need to stop her from going down to the O.R.
不好意思  我不认识你说的这个人
I'm sorry. I don't know who you're talking about.
是吗  那你老婆应该认识她吧
Oh, really? Well, maybe your wife does.
去啊  快去
Go. Go!
对不住了
Sorry.
罗丽
Lori.
谁放了你
Who set you free?
你是谁
Who are you?
算了
Fine.
一起死得了
I go, you go.
嘿  你醒了
Oh, hey. You're up.
我不太确定你是否想多睡会儿
I wasn't sure if you wanted to sleep in or not.
别吹了
Shut up!
真是受够了
I am so done with this shit.
用这个欧几里得矢量乘以
Then you multiplied the Euclidean vector
π的平方根的十七次方
by the square root of pi to the 17th power,
这样就得到了轴突点0.004
which then gives us an axon point of .004,
然后得到一个为8.2的线性平面矢量
then give us a linear plane vector of 8.2.
没了
Boom.
厉害
Damn.
如果这些是所有失败的算法
Well, if these are all the failed algorithms...
那就只剩下一种可能了
Then there's only one possibility left.
牛了个驴粪蛋蛋的  你做到了
Holy shit balls. You did it.
-什么  成功了吗  -太好了
- What? It worked? - Yes, yes, yes.
成功了  天啊  居然成功了
It worked? Oh, my God, it worked!
我们成功了
We did it!
激动个什么劲  我们都不认识她
Why are we so excited? We barely know her.
虽然我也不知道怎么回事
Honestly, I-I don't know what just happened,
但你写的那一黑板实在太酷了
but that was impressive.
谢谢
Thanks.
开干吧
Let's do this.
我们再确定一次
Just so we're totally clear,
一个变量会结束这个维度的时间循环
one variant closes the loop in this dimension,
而另一个变量则会把你送回原来的维度
and the other one sends you back to your original dimension
结束那边的循环
and closes that loop.
到最后决定的时间了
It's final decision time.
留下来  还是回去
Stay here or go back.
我留下
I'm staying here.
不会改的
Final decision.
好  那我们就开始了
Okay. Here we go, then.
往后退两步
Stand back.
等等
Wait.
怎么回事
What happened?
矢量出问题了
Oh, the vector's off.
你不是说是对的吗
But you said this was the right one.
不  公式没问题  是其他地方的毛病
No, the math was right. Something else is off.
各位  我为了替你们记住这些东西
Guys, I have literally been killing myself
不得不一遍又一遍的自杀
to memorize this shit for you.
我不接受失败这个结果
Failure's not an option.
怎么了
What?
硬盘有问题
There's something in hard drive.
肯定是病毒
It must be a virus.
老兄  你是不是又在电脑上看小黄片了
Dude, did you open spam porn again on the computer?
才没有咧
No.
完了  我得手动把程序输入一遍了
Great. I have to manually reenter all this code.
要多久
Okay, how long?
六  七个小时吧
Six, seven hours.
瑞恩  你看着我
Ryan, look at me.
我时间不多了
I am on borrowed time here.
听明白了吗
Understand?
你必须搞定它
Get it done.
嗯  我现在就在弄了
Uh, yeah, I'm on it.
翠  等等
Tree, wait up.
你确定要这么干吗
Hey. Are you sure about this?
当然确定了
Of course I'm sure.
那凶手怎么办
Okay, well, what about the killer?
你说今晚会有人死
I mean, you said people are gonna die tonight.
要是时间循环关闭了  而我们又不帮忙
If you close the loop and we don't help,
他们就死定了
then they're dead for good, aren't they?
我得活着
I have to stay alive.
那个医院太危险
I can't go back to that hospital.
我不会去的
It's way too risky.
就这样吗  你就眼睁睁看着
Okay, so that's it? You're just gonna walk away
无辜的人死掉吗
and let a bunch of innocent people die?
卡特  每天都有人死
People die every day, Carter.
不能都算在我头上吧
I can't be responsible for everyone, okay?
虽然听起来很自私  但理是就这个理
I know how selfish that sounds, but it's true.
不  这听起来可不是一般的自私
Yeah, no, that sounds incredibly selfish.
你认真的吗
Are you serious?
这不公平
That's not fair.
你根本不知道这对我有多难
You have no idea how hard this is for me.
我也不想在你跟我妈之间选
I don't want to have to choose between you and my mom,
可我就得选
but I have to.
什么叫"在我跟你妈之间选"
What do you mean, "choose"?
卡特  另一个维度中
Carter, we're together
我们俩在一起了
in the other dimension.
我每天都像今天一样
I woke up in your bed every morning,
在你床上醒过来
just like this morning.
我一遍又一遍地重复今天
I did it over and over and over again
最后爱上了你
until I fell in love with you.
可那是另一个维度发生的事情
But that version of us is back there,
我妈活着却是这个宇宙的事
and my mom is alive here.
所以我做出了选择
So I've made my decision.
那你错了怎么办
Wh... What if you're wrong?
如果你错了呢
What if you're wrong?
如果这不是
What if this isn't the life
你该过的生活  怎么办
that you're-you're supposed to have?
那又怎样  那我就活该回到
So, what? I'm just supposed to go back
我妈妈不在了的那个维度吗
to some dimension where my mom's dead?
我做不到
I can't.
我不想再失去她
I can't lose her again.
可你已经失去她了
You already did.
抹去这个事实的维度对你来说不算真实
And none of this is real if it erases that.
你只是在过着别人的生活
You're just... you're living someone else's life
这个生活不属于你
that doesn't belong to you.
你经历过的痛苦和失去
Y-Your pain, th-that loss, that's...
才成就了现在的你
that's what makes you you.
可你现在有机会做的事
But you have the chance to do something
别人却做梦才能梦到
other people only dream of.
什么事
What?
你还可以道别
You can say goodbye.
你女朋友叫你了
Your girlfriend's calling you.
我该走了
Better go.
她怎么了
What's her problem?
她居然不来我们的寝室会
She just ditched our house meeting.
喂
Hello.
你俩聊什么呢
What were you guys talking about?
没什么  就聊聊学校的事
Nothing. We were just... we were going over school stuff.
宝贝  可别忘了
Babe, don't forget,
我的美国文学论文还得靠你呢
I still need help with my American lit paper.
我  我现在真的没空
I'm... I'm really busy right now.
卡特  你答应过我的
Carter, you promised.
你不帮我的话  这门课我会挂的
I won't pass the class without your help.
好吧  行
All right. Yeah, yeah.
没问题
That's fine.
你人最好了
You're the best.
另一个女寿星到了
There's the other birthday girl.
亲爱的  你这是怎么了
Sweetie, what's wrong?
我没事  我
I'm okay. I...
你看起来可不太好
You don't look okay.
我没事  妈
I'm okay. I... Mom!
你浑身冷得跟冰一样
You're cold as ice.
要不我们去医院吧
Maybe we should go to the hospital.
不
No!
不行  不能去医院
No, we can't go there.
听着  我是不想吓到你们
Look, I don't want to freak you guys out,
但是我想要你们尽快离开学校
but I need you to get as far away from campus as possible.
-翠蕾莎  怎么了  -爸  拜托了
- Theresa, what is going on? - Dad, please.
我保证晚点会给你们解释的
I promise to explain everything later,
但是我需要你们相信我
but I need you to trust me.
行吧
Okay.
我们走吧
We'll go.
走吧  来
Let's go. Come on.
搞定
Done.
终于完事了
Finally.
你们准备好了吗
You guys ready?
好  让我们彻底关闭这个时间循环吧
Okay. Let's close this loop once and for all.
嘿  知道我现在特想吃点什么吗
Hey, you know what I'm craving right now?
-什么  -莫罗贝那家面包店有的
- What? - One of those giant cinnamon rolls
超大肉桂卷
from that bakery in Morro Bay.
我们去年生日吃过的啊
From our birthday last year?
不记得了吗  你还吃了两个呢
You don't remember? You ate two of them.
那不是我
That wasn't me.
说什么呢  亲爱的
What, sweetie?
嘿  姑娘们  天色有些晚了
Hey, girls, it's getting kind of late.
要不我们找个地方
What do you say we find someplace,
住一晚吧
turn in for the night?
行  听起来不错
Okay, sounds good.
我想大家都很累了
I think we're all pretty pooped.
(贝菲尔德供电站)
罗丽
Lori!
靠
Shit.
她被抓了  她被抓了
He got her, he got her!
不  别开枪  别开枪
No, don't shoot! Don't shoot!
你会打到凯的
You might hit Kay.
(系统准备好了  希望万事大吉)
姑娘们  我去拿点冰
Hey, girls, I'm gonna go get some ice.
马上回来
I'll be right back.
好了
Okay.
实话告诉我
Just tell me one thing.
你怀孕了吗
Are you pregnant?
什么
What?
没有  妈妈  我
No. Mom, I...
好吧  抱歉  但我必须得问
Okay, sorry. I just had to ask.
不是这样的
It's not like that.
但还是和男生有关  对吧
But it's a boy, isn't it?
不是
No.
算是吧
Yes.
我也不知道  事情有点复杂
I don't know. It's complicated.
相信我
Trust me.
多复杂我也能理解
I can do complicated.
是怎么回事
What is it?
你有没有想过如果没有和爸爸在一起的话
Have you ever wondered what your life would have been like
你会有怎样的生活
if you couldn't be with Dad?
什么  没想过
What? No.
但如果你必须做出选择呢
But what if you had to choose?
就是  如果跟他在一起
You know, what if... what if being with him meant
你就会失去和你一个非常亲密的人
that you would lose someone that you were really close to,
而且再也见不到那个人
that you would never get to see that person ever again?
那你会怎么做
What would you do?
我们都有要做出艰难选择的时候  翠
Well, we all have to make hard choices, Tree.
这就是生活
That's life.
有时候  过去会牵引我们往一个方向走
And sometimes the past is pulling us in one direction
而未来却在另一个方向召唤我们
and the future is calling us somewhere new.
但是毫无疑问  如果必须选择
But, of course, if I had to choose,
我会选你爸爸
I'd pick Daddy.
我是说  没有他也就不会有你  对吧
I mean, without him, I wouldn't have you, right?
但你怎么知道他就是命中注定的那一个呢
But how did you know that he was the one?
我并不知道
I didn't.
我只是碰碰运气
I took a chance.
遵从自己的心意
I followed my heart.
这就是爱  翠
That's kind of how love works, Tree.
也就是放手一搏
It's a leap of faith.
在贝菲尔德大学医院
...Bayfield University Hospital,
惨案仍在发生
where a terrible tragedy continues to unfold.
相关信息陆续公开
Details are still coming in,
截至目前已确认三名受害者
but so far, we can confirm three victims.
一名护士和一名警察被害
A nurse and a police officer.
第三名受害者是个学生
The third victim, a student,
在试图制服嫌疑犯时不幸遇害
was killed while attempting to subdue the suspect.
以上是前线报道  主持人
Back to you, Dan.
不
No.
怎么了
What's wrong?
快点电话  瑞恩  快接
Come on, Ryan. Come on.
萨玛  能帮忙
Hey, Samar, can you
-查一下22 97 39吗  -好的
- check 22-97-39 right there? - Uh, yeah.
那边
Over there.
等等  矢量需要调整一下
No, the vector needs to be adjusted.
哟  我是瑞恩  听到哔声后请留言
Yo, it's Ryan. Leave a message at the beep...
瑞恩  不要关闭时间循环
Ryan, don't close the loop.
-你不能  -抱歉
- You can't... - I'm sorry.
-语音信箱已满  -靠
- This voice mailbox is... - Shit!
翠  发生什么事了
Tree, what is going on?
我不能让他关闭循环
I can't let him close it.
我说不准这冰是怎么了
You know, I'm not sure about this ice.
闻起来像尿一样
It kind of smells like pee.
翠
Tree?
翠  你去哪里
Tree! Where are you going?
翠
Tree!
快接电话
Come on.
快接电话  接电话  快接电话
Come on, come on! Pick up your phone!
-哟  我是瑞恩 听到  -操
- Yo, it's Ryan. Leave a... - Shit!
开始吧
Here we go.
在哪里  快点  快点
Where is it? Come on, come on, come on. Please.
嘿  你醒了
Oh, hey. You're up.
我不太确定你是否想多睡会儿
I wasn't sure if you wanted to sleep in or not.
那是我最后一次为你去死
That is the last time I'm dying for you.
什么
What?
还要多久时间
How much longer is it gonna take?
多亏你惊人的记忆力  应该用不了多久
Thanks to your crazy memory, it shouldn't take long at all.
几分钟后就可以让西西装置准备就绪
I can have Sissy ready to go in just a few minutes.
我还需要一点点时间
I need a little more time.
我还有些事要做
There's something I need to do.
翠
Tree.
你确定要回去吗
You sure you want to go back?
总不能一辈子活在过去里
Can't spend my life living in the past.
要有点信心放手一搏
Got to take a leap of faith.
可算回来了
She finally rolls in.
罗丽  你好
Lori, hi.
昨晚很忙吧
Big night?
差不多吧
You could say that.
听着  罗丽  我
Um, look, Lori, I...
见到你很开心
It's good to see you.
什
Wha...
我也很开心能见到你  翠
It's good to see you, too, Tree.
他不值得
He's not worth it.
我是说  相信我
I mean, trust me.
我也曾和一个已婚男人有一腿
I've been involved with a married guy.
也清楚以双重身份生活是什么滋味
I know what it's like living a double life.
总是觉得自己很差劲
Always feeling like shit about yourself.
但是浪子回头金不换
But it's never too late to change.
曾经有人和我说
Someone once told me that
"每一天都是一个让自己更优秀的机会"
"every day is a chance to be someone better."
或许今天就是你变得更优秀的日子
Maybe this is your day.
好吧
Okay.
谢谢你
Thank you.
照顾好自己
Take care of yourself.
翠
Tree.
嘿
Hey.
那个  丹妮尔  我很难过
Um... look, Danielle, I feel really bad.
之前一直误会你
I've totally been misjudging you,
都是我的错
and it's completely on me.
-我很抱歉  我想把  -赞啊
- I am so sorry that I've, like, made this... - Nice.
三人行
Three-way.
他开玩笑呢
He's kidding.
不  我没开玩笑
No, I'm-I'm not.
尼克的  呃  花洒坏了
Nick's, um, shower was broken,
所以我让他借用我的
so I said he could use mine.
对吧  尼克
Right, Nick?
我的花洒好着呢
My shower's fine.
好吧  那个  当我没说
Right. Um, you know what? Never mind.
抱歉打扰你们了
Sorry for interrupting.
拜拜
Bye-ee.
打我干嘛
What was that for?
因为你蠢得跟石头一样
For being dumb as a rock. That's what.
哦  是吗  石头怎么会蠢
Oh, really? How can a rock be dumb?
他们连脑子都没有
They don't even have brains.
另一个女寿星到了
There's the other birthday girl.
-你好啊  亲爱的  -你好  老爸
-Hi, sweetie. - Hey, Dad.
能让我和妈妈单独聊两句吗
Um, do you mind if I talk to Mom alone for a minute?
就是些女孩间的私房话
Just some girl talk.
当然可以了
Oh. Well, sure.
那我去打几个工作电话
I-I can go run some work calls.
好的  谢谢
Okay, thanks.
一切都还好吗
Is everything okay?
嗯  都很好
Yeah. It's fine.
一切都好
Everything's fine.
糟糕  我要怎么开口
Oh, shit, how do I do this?
说什么  亲爱的  怎么了
Do what, sweetie? What's wrong?
妈妈
Mom...
我真想让你知道我有多爱你
I really want you to know how much I love you.
我也好爱你  亲爱的
I love you, too, sweetie.
不是的  妈妈  我是认真的
No, Mom, I'm serious.
人们总是说 我爱你
You know, people say "I love you"
但是
all the time, but...
只有在你无法再次当面说出这句话的时候
it's not until you can't say it to that person's face anymore
才会发现自己有多深爱着对方
that you really realize how much you mean it.
你如此完美又如此漂亮
You are so beautiful and so amazing.
我只希望有一天
And I just hope I can become
我能有你一半的好
half of the woman that you are one day.
你是在说笑吗
Are you kidding?
因为有了你  我才变成了现在的自己
I'm the woman I am because I had you.
这话我还从没对其他人说过
You know, I never really told anyone this before,
当我怀上你的时候  我吓得手足无措
but when I was pregnant with you, I was scared shitless.
不
No.
但当我抱着你的时候
But then, the moment I held you,
我内心的某些部分就立刻改变了
something inside of me changed instantly.
最伟大的爱就是这样
The best kind of love does that.
它会改变你
It changes you.
使你成为一个更好的人
It makes you a better person.
天啊  我太笨了
Oh, God, I'm so stupid.
我真的以为我可以拥有一切  但我不能
I really thought I could have it all, but I can't.
亲爱的  没人可以拥有一切
Oh, honey, nobody can.
但你猜怎么着
But guess what.
这没关系
That's okay.
你会得到你需要的
You'll get what you need.
我希望如此
I hope so.
过来吧
Aw. Come here.
我压着你了吗
Am I crushing you?
没有
Nope.
你永远是我的小女儿
You're always gonna be my little girl.
∮ 祝你生日快乐 ∮
∮ Happy birthday to you
∮ 祝翠和妈妈生日快乐 ∮
∮ Happy birthday, Tree and Mom
∮ 祝你生日快乐 ∮
∮ Happy birthday to you.
许个愿吧
Make a wish.
准备好了吗
You ready?
等等
Wait.
听我说
Look...
我知道这可能非常令人困惑
I know this is probably pretty confusing.
我是说  你们认识我才几个小时
I mean, you guys have only known me for a couple hours,
但我已经认识你们几个星期了
but I've known you for weeks.
你们都很努力地
You've all worked really, really hard
试图帮我送回家
to try to send me home.
所以谢谢你们
So thank you.
陪审团仍在讨论你是否完全疯了
Well, jury's still out on whether you're totally nuts,
但很高兴我们能帮上忙
But I glad we could help.
好了  瑞恩  启动吧
Okay, Ryan, light her up.
所以  在另一个维度  我们
S-So, in this other dimension, do we...
我们认识吗
do we know each other?
你可以这么说
You could say that.
17秒
17 seconds.
16  15  14
sixteen, fifteen, fourteen...
我是怎么跟你说的  不要打开那个东西
What did I tell you about turning that thing on?
等一下  这还不应该发生
Uh-oh. Wait. This isn't supposed to happen yet.
你应该明天才来
You're not supposed to come until tomorrow.
现在把那东西关掉
Turn that thing off now.
不  不要
No, don't!
不  不  不
No, no, no, no! No, no!
不  求你了  你不能这样做
No, wait, please. You can't do this.
-你是谁  -我是这里的学生
- And who are you? - I am a student here.
好吧  如果你继续是这样的态度
Oh, well, keep this little attitude up,
你很快就不是了
and we'll change that.
把那东西拿出去
Get that thing out of here.
-不  请不要  -小心点  猛男
- No, please d-don't. - Hey, watch it, beefcake.
别这样  我们花了18个月在它身上
Don't. Don't. We spent 18 months on that thing.
求你了  求你了  别这样
Please, please don't. Please.
别这么粗暴
Well, don't manhandle her.
拿
Take...
你要把她带去哪儿
Well, where are you taking her?
我要把它锁在我的办公室里
My office, where it will remain under lock and key.
好吧  这是个挫折  我明白
Look, okay, it's a setback. I get it.
但我们可以重新过一遍今天  再试一次
Right, but we just reset the day and try again.
不  你不明白
No. You don't understand.
每次回来我都越来越虚弱
I keep getting weaker every time I come back.
我不知道我还有多少机会
I don't know how many chances I have left.
据我所知  这可能就是最后一次机会了
For all I know, this could be it.
如果我这一次死了  我也不能复活了
If I die again, I could stay dead.
-这可是个大问题  -操蛋
- Hmm, that's a problem. - Oh shit.
除非
Unless...
除非我们把它偷回来
Unless we steal it back.
偷回来吗
Steal it?
我是说  你知道的
Well, I mean, you know,
严格说  这甚至都不算偷窃  不是吗
it's not even technically stealing, is it?
这是你们的东西
It's your property.
伙计们  我可不知道
Whoa, whoa, guys, I don't know about this.
如果我们被抓了  我被开除了
Like, if we get caught and I get expelled,
我父母可是要把我吊在麻袋边往死里打的
my parents are gonna hang me by the nut sack.
我加入他
I'm with him.
当然不是说一起当麻袋
Except for the "nut sack" part, obviously.
你在开玩笑吧
Are you kidding me? Are...
不  我很抱歉在这里我
No. I'm sorry to throw a bag of dog shit
要倒戈相向了  但我
on your front porch here, but I...
这全都怪你们
This is all on you guys.
你们弄了这个烂摊子
You created this mess,
所以你们有义务帮助她摆脱困境
so you're obligated to help her out of it.
另外  如果她今晚又死了
Besides, if she dies again tonight,
你们都脱不了关系
that's blood on your hands.
这可有点戏剧性
That's a little dramatic.
他说的对
He's right.
这是我们的错
This is our fault.
所以我们得纠正它
So we fix it.
科学家就得这么做
That's what scientists do.
科学家专门解决问题
We solve the problem.
布洛森院长的办公室就在这幢楼里
So, Dean Bronson's office is in this building here,
回到实验室最快的就是这条路
and the fastest route back to the lab is this path here.
看看这个  伙计们  布洛森院长
And check this out, guys. Dean Bronson spends
每天晚上都在教员休息室里织毛衣
every evening knitting in the faculty lounge over here.
等等  什么  织毛衣吗
Wait, what? He knits?
我以为他在那里抽烟
I think he used to smoke,
然后他的妻子让他戒烟  而且
and then his wife made him quit, and, uh...
顺便说一句  他妻子太火辣了
Oh, by the way, shockingly hot.
萨玛
Samar?
我们能
Could we do the-the thing we're...
专注一点吗
we're doing right now?
好吧  对不起  没问题
Right. Sorry. Um, okay.
所以  我们需要拿到他办公室的钥匙
So, we need to get the keys to his office,
然后溜到招生处  闯进院长办公室
sneak over to admissions, break into the dean's office,
拿到西西装置  把她带回实验室
grab Sissy, wheel her back to the lab
还不能让安保人员看到我们
without anyone from security seeing us,
还需要把布洛森院长的钥匙还给他
get Dean Bronson's keys back to him
但不能让他知道钥匙被偷了
without him ever knowing they were gone,
给西西装置通电  运行程序
power up Sissy, run diagnostics,
打开开关  砰的一声  翠就回去了
flip the switch, and bam... Tree's back
回到她来的那个古怪的维度
in whatever wack-ass dimension she came from,
我们  我们就挽救了这该死的一天
and we... well, we just saved the damn day.
可以
Okay.
听起来棒极了
Sounds awesome.
-我们怎么做到这个计划  -我不知道
- How do we do that? - I don't know.
-你当然不知道  -好吧  好吧
- Of course. - Okay, well,
我们显然需要转移院长的注意力
we obviously need a diversion.
所以我们得想个办法分散他的注意力
So we just got to find a way to distract Dean Bronson.
她选的铃声  好吗  我
Uh, she picked the ringtone, all right? I...
嘿  宝贝
Hey, babe.
是的  你还好吗
Yeah, uh, you okay?
-我有个主意  -你说
- I-I have an idea. - Okay.
如果我们从这边过去呢
What if we actually go through...
我在和瑞恩还有他们还有
With Ryan and them and...
-丹妮尔  你好啊  -她不是
- Danielle, hi. - She's not...
我们要请你帮个小忙
So, we have a little favor to ask.
我也觉得可疑
I feel suspect at best.
让我们把脸放过去
Let's just put our face in.
嘿  宝贝
Hey, baby.
好吧  对不起
Oh. Okay, sorry.
显然  她有点紧张
Clearly, she's a little on edge.
-说的对  -给她一些喘息的空间
- That's right. - Give her some room to breathe...
瞎说
Preach.
需要我帮助你吗
Can I help you?
(西语)抱歉
Oh, perdón.
我似乎  呃  迷路了
I appear to be, uh, very lost.
我是罗杰·布洛森  学校的院长
Roger Bronson. I'm the dean of the school.
(法语)哦  你好
Oh, bonjour.
我的名字是  呃  爱美莉·勒·皮尤
My name is, uh, Amélie Le Pew.
你一定是交换生吧
Oh. You must be with the exchange program.
(法语)啊  是的
Ah, oui, oui.
先生  我能摸摸你的脸吗
Monsieur, may I know your face?
你说什么
I'm sorry?
-好吧  -我的天呐
- My. Oh, my. - Oh, my!
容貌真有特色
What strong features.
谢谢您
Thank you.
你一定是法国人
You must be French.
你的手闻起来像奶酪
Your hand smells like cheese.
我不吃奶酪
I don't eat cheese.
我有  呃
Ah, I am, uh...
乳糖不耐症
...uh, lactose intolerant.
(法语)哦  真遗憾
Oh, quelle dommage.
你想去哪里
Uh, uh... uh, where are you trying to get to?
(法语)呃  咖啡馆
Uh, le café.
你一定是指餐厅吧
Oh, you must mean the cafeteria.
我很乐意给你指路  走这边  我可以
I'm happy to show you. Here, here. I can... Uh, whoa!
别动  你会绊倒的
Oh, oh! Oh, don't move! You'll trip.
哦  弹珠
Oh, marbles.
弹珠  到处都是弹珠
Marbles! Marbles everywhere.
快走
Go, go, go, go.
哦  天呐
Oh, boy.
小心点
Careful.
走的很快啊
Pretty quick there.
等一下好吗  别动  好吗
Hold on, now. Just stay put, okay?
我只需要  呃  拿上我的钥匙
I just need to, uh, grab my keys.
哦  别碰挂毯
Oh! Not the tapestry.
哦  天哪
Oh, geez.
哦  上帝啊  哦  哦  不
Oh. Oh, Lord. Oh, oh, oh! Oh, no!
哦  不  太黑了
Oh, no. It's so dark.
向灯光方向移动
Move toward the light.
哦  对不起  说错话了
Oh, sorry, that was insensitive.
来吧
Come on.
-快点  快点  -我在努力
- Come on, come on, come on. - I'm trying.
别滚动了  好吗
Stop rolling. Okay.
你是在帮倒忙  滚反了
You're not helping. The other way.
-西西装置  -快带走
- Sissy. - Go, go.
走  快走
Go around, go around.
这边
This way.
萨玛  萨玛
Samar. Samar.
好的  好了
Okay, okay.
好了  起来  起来
Here we go. Up. Up.
哦  天哪
Oh, God.
这是你的拐杖
Here's your cane.
你真的不能再到处乱跑了
You really must stop wandering around.
-(西语)谢谢  -好了  走吧
- Gracias. - Okay. Okay. Shall we?
忘记带钥匙了
Ah, forgot my keys.
-天呐  -(法语)哦不  我的上帝
- Oh, God! - Oh, no, mon Dieu.
天呐
God!
我流了好多血
Oh, that's a lot of blood.
天呐  小心点用你的拐杖
Jesus, be careful with that thing.
-我很抱歉  -我的天啊
- I am so sorry. - Oh, my God.
我觉得使用拐杖对你来说不是个好主意
Oh, I don't think the cane is a good idea for you.
你需要一只导盲犬
You need a Seeing Eye dog.
将军咯
Checkmate.
情况如何了
Hey. How's it going?
正在努力
We're on it.
老兄  还剩下不到三个小时了
Guys, we've got less than three hours
赶紧让它启动啊
to make this happen.
我不骗你  马上就完事了
Not gonna lie... it's gonna be close.
妈的
Shit.
如果不阻止凶手的话  罗丽会死的
If I don't stop the killer, Lori's gonna die.
你守在这里
Stay here.
什么  你要干什么
What? Why?
别管  只要保证你会守在这里就行
Just promise me you'll stay here.
能借用一下吗
Can I borrow this?
呃  当然  随便
Uh, y-yeah, sure.
好的
Okay.
等等  你要去哪里
W-Wait, where are you going?
翠
Tree!
抱歉  来的挺不是时候的
Sorry, bad timing.
好吧  好吧
Okay. Okay.
行吧  允许你把它收起来
Okay, you can put it away.
快点的  塞回去
Come on, put it away.
现在把身子慢慢的转过来
Okay, now slowly turn around.
你这是在犯下大错
This is a really bad idea.
医院里现有个杀人狂魔出没
There's a killer on the loose here.
快去找点援手
Go get help.
-你说什么  -快走
- What? - Go!
这个女的有枪  这女的有枪啊
She's got a gun! She's got a gun!
罗丽  让开
Lori, move.
-什么鬼  -快点  我们该走了
- What? - Come on, we've got to move.
-到底怎么回事  -路上解释  快走
- What's happening? - I'll explain later. Move!
这什么情况
What is this?
你根本不瞎
You're not blind.
我要弄死他们
I'm gonna kill them.
我一定要弄死他们
I'm going to kill them!
他朝你们去了
He's onto us.
宝贝  能帮忙把我太阳眼镜拿回来了吗
Babe, can you also get my sunglasses back?
还没戴热乎呢
I just got those.
-使劲啊使劲  快点  -知道
- Okay, okay, come on. - Yes.
给我弄开
Get it open now.
快点  快点
Get it, get it.
给我撞啊
Bash it in.
-别让他们进来  -我们在努力了
- Keep 'em out. -We're trying!
赶紧给我弄开
Get it open now!
要是被开除了  父母会和我断绝关系的
Oh, my God. If I get expelled, my parents are gonna disown me.
翠  能行行好告诉我到底怎么回事吗
Tree, will you please tell me what's going on?
一开始我只是单纯的以为他想杀我
At first, I thought he was trying to kill me,
-但没想到目标其实是你  -谁的目标
- but it's you he's after. - Who?
格瑞格里  到此为止了
It's over, Gregory.
什么  为什么会是你
What? Why?
他老婆发现了你跟他搞外遇
His wife found out about your affair.
所以他就照抄了你之前的方法
So he stole a page from your old playbook.
他先把汤布斯放了  这样大家就会
He set Tombs free, knowing that everyone
认为他才是罪魁祸首
would think that he killed you.
再把你弄死  劈腿的事就无人知晓了
And the secret of your affair would die with you.
精彩
Bravo.
真是精彩至极啊
Well done, indeed.
一日偷吃  终身为贼
Once a douchebag, always a douchebag.
不好意思  您是哪根葱
I'm sorry, do I know you?
别动  你个禽兽
Stay back, asshole.
把吃奶的劲也给我用上
Put your back into it!
再使使劲啊
Try harder.
你俩这点小劲对得起身上的肉吗
You guys got to get back into the gym, man.
瑞恩  我们快撑不住了
Ryan, we can't hold it much longer.
快点  快点啊
Come on, come on.
听到了吗
You hear that?
马上你就得把牢底坐穿了
You're gonna rot in prison.
我可不这么想哦
I don't think so.
你的推理漏掉了那么一个细节
You see, there's one little detail
百密的这一疏会让你满盘皆输
you failed to realize in all this.
真的吗  我漏掉了什么呢
Oh, really? What's that?
我啊
Me.
罗丽
Lori!
你难不成还真以为
You really think I was gonna let
我会乖乖等着这个婊子毁掉我的生活吗
a little whore like that ruin my life?
格瑞格里  利索点
Gregory, kill her.
超度的重任就交给你了
Would you like to do the honors?
荣幸之至
Don't mind if I do.
哦  等等  我差点忘了
Oh, wait. I almost forgot.
我想和你离婚了
I want a divorce.
好吧  说到哪里了
Now, where were we?
嘿
Hey!
真可悲  你是想用这个螺丝刀戳死我吗
Aw, look who brought a screwdriver to a gunfight.
等会
Wait.
我还需要告诉你一个事
I have something I need to tell you.
什么事
What?
你死定了
You're screwed.
你个贱人  快把它关掉
Turn it off, you bitch.
不不不  等  等等
No. No, no, no, no, no, no, wait. Wait!
准备好了吗  来吧
Ready? Come on.
你能行的  我撑着你
There you go. I got you.
没事的
I got you.
好嘞  大功告成
All right. Yep.
我的天啊  你还好吧
Oh, my God. Are you okay?
这地方挨个枪子都跟破了个皮似的
I guess this is a pretty good place to get shot, huh?
我要把你抱起来了  好吗
I'll lift you up now, all right?
你会没事的  你很坚强
You're gonna be okay. You're good.
慢一点  慢一点
It's okay, it's okay.
你会好起来的
You're okay.
罗丽  我
Lori, I...
我真心感到抱歉
I'm so sorry.
道什么歉呢
For what?
你可是我的救命恩人啊
You just saved my life.
我只是
I just...
我希望事情原本可以有所不同
I wish things could have been different.
打扰一下  我们得开始转移了
I'm sorry, but we need to move her.
坚持住啊
Hang in there, hon.
嘿
Hey.
你没事吧
Hey. You okay?
呃  没有
Uh, yeah.
没事  我没事  我只是
Yeah, I'm fine. I...
我记得告诉过你不要来医院
I thought I told you to stay put.
啊哈  确实
Yeah, well...
抱歉  忍不住就来了
sorry, couldn't help myself.
看来到时候了
I think it's time.
我希望你知道  我回来只是为了一件事
I hope you realize I'm only going back for one reason.
我的妈啊
Oh, man.
我的饮料啊
My Yoo-hoo.
丹妮尔
Danielle?
咋回事啊
Who?
你好啊
Hi.
卧槽等等  我好像拉裤子了
Oh, my God. I think I just shit my pants.
∮ 活着  就是图个痛快 ∮
∮ Ah, ah, ah, ah Stayin' alive... ooh... yeah ∮
∮ 从哥的脚步中就看得出来 ∮
∮ Whoo, well, you can tell by the way I use my walk ∮
∮ 哥是大众情人  不必多说 ∮
∮ I'm a woman, no time to talk ∮
∮ 音乐很吵 女孩很躁 ∮
∮ Music loud and women warm, I've been kicked around ∮
∮ 打从娘胎里出来哥就在四处游荡 ∮
∮ Since I was born ∮
∮ 现在气氛刚刚好 ∮
∮ And now it's all right, it's okay ∮
∮ 你可以换个角度去思考 ∮
∮ And you may look the other way ∮
∮ 给我使劲的思考 ∮
∮ We can try to understand Uh-huh, uh-huh ∮
∮ 纽约时报都对咱干了啥好事 ∮
∮ The New York Times' effect on man ∮
∮ 无论你是抠脚大汉  还是贵为人母 ∮
∮ Whether you're a brother or whether you're a mother ∮
∮ 你都实实在在地活着  痛快地活着 ∮
∮ You're stayin' alive, stayin' alive ∮
∮ 城市在发展  人们在律动 ∮
∮ Feel the city breakin' and everybody shakin' ∮
∮ 我们都实实在在地活着  痛快活着 ∮
∮ And we're stayin' alive, stayin' alive ∮
∮ 活着 就要享受生活 ∮
∮ Ah, ah, ah, ah stayin' alive, stayin' alive ∮
∮ 活着  就是图个痛快 ∮
∮ Ah, ah, ah, ah stayin' alive ∮
∮ 现如今  哥在人海中浮浮沉沉 ∮
∮ Well, now, I get low and I get high ∮
∮ 虽高不成低不就  但哥真的很努力 ∮
∮ And if I can't get either, I really try ∮
∮ 哥可是鞋上长翅膀的男人 ∮
∮ Got the wings of heaven on my shoes ∮
∮ 骚起舞来  谁与争锋 ∮
∮ I'm dancin' and I just can't lose ∮
∮ 现在气氛刚刚好 ∮
∮ And now it's all right, it's okay ∮
∮ 哥会笑着看到明天的太阳 ∮
∮ I'll live to see another day ∮
∮ 给我使劲的琢磨 ∮
∮ We can try to understand ∮
∮ 纽约时报都对咱干了啥好事 ∮
∮ The New York Times' effect on man ∮
∮ 无论你是抠脚大汉  还是贵为人母 ∮
∮ Whether you're a brother or whether you're a mother ∮
∮ 你都实实在在地活着  痛快地活着 ∮
∮ You're stayin' alive, stayin' alive ∮
∮ 城市在发展  人们在律动 ∮
∮ Feel the city breakin' and everybody shakin' ∮
∮ 我们都实实在在地活着  痛快活着 ∮
∮ And we're stayin' alive, stayin' alive ∮
∮ 活着  就要享受生活 ∮
∮ Ah, ah, ah, ah stayin' alive, stayin' alive ∮
∮ 活着  就得图个痛快 ∮
∮ Ah, ah, ah, ah stayin' alive ∮
∮ 我只想痛痛快快地活着 ∮
∮ I'm stayin' alive ∮
∮ 生活将去向何方  谁懂哥的寂寞 ∮
∮ Life goin' nowhere. Somebody help me ∮
∮ 有谁懂哥的寂寞 ∮
∮ Somebody help me, yeah ∮
∮ 我只想痛快地活着 ∮
∮ I'm stayin' alive ∮
∮ 生活将去向何方 谁懂哥的寂寞 ∮
∮ Life goin' nowhere. Somebody help me, yeah ∮
∮ 有谁能懂哥的寂寞 ∮
∮ Somebody help me, yeah ∮
∮ 生活将去向何方  谁懂哥深沉的寂寞 ∮
∮ Life goin' nowhere. Somebody help me, yeah. ∮
根本没道理啊
Just doesn't make any sense.
当然有道理啊
Yes, it does.
这就像个弹弓似的
It acted like a slingshot.
当她跳回这个维度时
When she jumped back into this dimension,
向心力产生的真空会使时间循环闭合
the vacuum created by the centripetal force closed the loop.
谁这么造孽把这么完好的小油条扔地上了
Who throws away a perfectly good churro?
噢你别  别吃啊
Oh, no, don't.
啊哦  看上去有点不妙
Uh-oh. This looks bad.
你是瑞恩 凡吗
Ryan Phan?
呃  好像是我吧
Uh, maybe.
我是艾萨克·帕克博士  代表美国国防高级研究计划局(DARPA)
I'm Dr. Isaac Parker. I'm here on behalf of DARPA.
如果你能配合我们进行一些调查
We'd appreciate it if you'd come with us
我们将不胜感激
to answer some questions.
你们所有人
All of you.
我们惹了什么麻烦吗
Are we in trouble?
好了  这边请
Please, right this way.
卡利巴托博士请到人工智能区
Dr. Kalibato to Robotics.
卧了个大槽
Holy shit.
西西装置
Sissy.
希望你们不介意我们征用了她
Hope you don't mind us borrowing her.
你们在这里的所作所为令人叹为观止
What you've created here is truly remarkable.
一边玩去吧  布洛森院长
Suck it, Dean Bronson.
我们在研究这个装置时
We've been having some difficulties
遇到了一些困难
understanding how the device operates.
我觉得你们能帮上忙
We figured you could help.
这个有很多不同的算法
There's so many different algorithms.
很难找到合适的方法能让它稳定发挥作用
It'll be tough to find the right one to make it work.
我也许能帮上忙哦
I might be able to help with that.
很好
Great.
所以  我们只缺一个测试对象了
So, we just need to find a test subject.
等等  你们是想把人困在时间循环里吗
Wait, you... you want to trap somebody in a time loop?
这太扯淡了
That's messed up.
当然除非有人活该
Unless they deserve it.
我想到了个完美的候选人
I think I have the perfect recruit.